readersdigest.ca 2007-07-27

# Reader's Digest Canada - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

In over 75 years in the Direct Marketing business, Reader's Digest has adhered to the highest standards in assuring our customers' privacy. All information -- including customer accounts, transactions, and all correspondence, are handled with the utmost discretion. 

The policies below are applicable to Readers Digest Magazines Canada Limited and to www.ourcanada.ca and www.readersdigest.ca, owned and operated by The Reader's Digest Association (Canada) Ltd., unless otherwise indicated. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
The only personal information collected by Reader's Digest through our web sites is information which is submitted to us voluntarily and knowingly by site visitors. When you simply browse our site, no personal information is being collected by Reader's Digest. 

Some functions and services offered through our site require that you provide certain personal information, for example, when you order a product, enter a contest or sweepstakes, request a catalog, or register for a mailing list, we may need your postal or e-mail address. 

**Receiving E-mail and Postal Correspondence**  
By submitting a form on this site you will be entitled to receive e-mail correspondence from Reader's Digest. This e-mail correspondence may include opportunities to enter sweepstakes as well as subscriber-only special offers, including discounts, free gifts, and opportunities to win cash and prizes. You may opt out of being included in our mailing list by updating your communications preferences by clicking here. Our purpose is to provide visitors with useful information and offers that will interest them. Every e-mail we send out will include an explanation on how to opt-out from receiving future e-mail correspondence. 

Reader's Digest will not share e-mail addresses we collect through our web sites with any unaffiliated third parties unless we specify at the point of collection. Occasionally, Reader's Digest may make names and postal addresses we collect through our web sites available to reputable companies whose products and/or services may interest you unless you opt out of being included in our postal mailing list. 

Reader's Digest may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third parties for statistical analysis, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**Opting Out**  
Receiving e-mail messages from Reader's Digest is optional. You may choose not to receive e-mail, even after granting prior permission, or you may wish to correct information you previously provided. If you do not wish to receive e-mail or wish to correct information you provided to Reader's Digest, please click here to go to the Communications Preferences Form. 

Reader's Digest will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete records from our database when we receive requests to do so; however because of possible retention of a residual copy in a system backup file, we cannot guarantee deletion in every instance. 

If you prefer not to receive postal mailings from Reader's Digest or from reputable companies we may share your name and postal address with, write to us at the address below. 

**Communicating by Postal Mail**  
If you prefer to contact Reader's Digest by regular postal mail, please write to: 

Reader's Digest Association (Canada) Ltd.  
Customer Services  
1125 Stanley Street  
Montreal, QC H3B 5H5 

You may use the address above for general customer service questions. You may also use this address to communicate that you'd prefer not to receive Reader's Digest mailings and/or mailings from other companies to which we make our postal mailing list available. 

**Online Policy for Individuals Under 18 Years Old**  
No personal information should be submitted or posted at Reader's Digest Online Web Sites by individuals under 18 years of age. 

No information collected from online guests 17 years of age or under is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever by Reader's Digest. Unless otherwise disclosed at collection, Reader's Digest does not provide any personally identifying information collected through our web sites from individuals 17 years old and under, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. 

Note to parents: If your child has submitted his or her name through a Reader's Digest web site, and you wish to review that information, to have it corrected or deleted from our records, or to refuse to permit further collection or use of the children's information, please communicate your wishes to us at the address above. Reader's Digest pledges to exert reasonable efforts to assure that the information is deleted as soon as possible. 

We encourage parents to be aware of their children's online activities, and to learn about software that can filter objectionable materials. 

**Advertisers**  
If you submit your name through a form on a Reader's Digest web site to request information from an advertiser or other third party, Reader's Digest is not responsible for any marketing or other use of your name by the third party. To learn more about any other company or organization's privacy policies, we suggest visiting their web site or contacting them by postal mail or telephone. 

**E-mail messages**  
If you send Reader's Digest an e-mail message, we may retain that message and your e-mail address, as well as any response we send you. 

**Hyperlinks to Other Web Sites**  
Reader's Digest web sites may include links to web sites of other companies unaffiliated with Reader's Digest. Please note that we are unable to review all such sites and take no responsibility for the content of any unaffiliated web site. 

**Cookies and Server Logs**  
Reader's Digest, related web hosting providers, and advertisers sometimes utilize "cookie" technology. Cookies are bits of data stored on your local hard drive which help enhance your web browsing experience. Not all web browsers accept cookies, and those that do usually provide a preference or setting which allow to refuse cookies. If your browser does not accept cookies, you may not be able to fully participate in all our web sites' features, including registration and entry into contests, prize draws and sweepstakes. 

Server logs capture certain non-personally identifying data, such as the time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is used in aggregate form to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our visitors' web browsing systems. 

**Credit Cards**  
Reader's Digest uses credit card numbers submitted to us through our web sites for payment purposes only, and not for marketing purposes. We utilize industry standard secure encryption technology to reasonably assure the privacy and security of the credit card numbers of anyone who places online orders with us. 

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions**  
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at anytime. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of Reader's Digest on-line sites following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.
